词典: C:\Users\DR\Downloads\DSH\hackmud-zh-mod\dict\zh.json  (992 条)

[译]   <color=#9B9B9BFF>help</color>           [see this again]
     -> help                            [再次查看此帮助]

[译]   <color=#9B9B9BFF>clear</color>          [clear the window]
     -> clear                          [清空窗口]

[译] The second most important thing, after making money, is spending it. Cuz you gotta spend money to make money.
     -> 第二重要的事——仅次于赚钱——就是花钱。因为想赚钱，就得先花钱。

[译] Obtain and provide a verification code to this script  以继续。 Obtaining this code is left as an exercise for yourself. Thank you for your co-operation.
     -> 获取一个验证码并提供给这个脚本，以继续。获取验证码这件事，就留给你自己当练习了。感谢你的配合。

[原] Top level marks are available to earn now, run marks.Èmark_nameÉ to begin a mark

[原] name: "Èmark_nameÉ" - Search for mark by name

[原] pos: [x,y] - View mark at specified coordinates

[原] Will you be able to trust 3 alpha H!T forever?

[原] even if not a vac,   you are at least friend of _2_11_45_36! maybe even worthy of truth!

[原] mark :::running_in_the_pool::: hC¨ been hidden

