词典: C:\Users\DR\Downloads\DSH\hackmud-zh-mod\dict\zh.json  (1230 条)

[译] The second most important thing, after making money, is spending it.
     -> 第二重要的事——仅次于赚钱——就是花钱。

[译] Cuz you gotta spend money to make money.
     -> 因为想赚钱，就得先花钱。

[译] Top level marks are available to earn now, run marks.<mark_name> to begin a mark
     -> 顶层标记现在都可以获取了，运行 marks.<mark_name> 即可开始一个标记

[译] Of course, life in the pool is not without transactional loss. You receive 
     -> 当然，池子里的生活并非没有交易损耗。你收到

[译]  of those units. The lifeguard took around 25%. He is a good lifeguard.
     -> 个该单位。 救生员抽走了大约 25%。他是个好救生员。

